我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来  我只是个普通的鉴证专员
To the outside world, I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
but secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
我秘密地打击犯罪  寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
我让杀害母亲的凶手自食其果
I hunted down the man who killed my mother,
但我们的世界也因此出现了新的威胁
but in doing so, I opened up our world to new threats,
我是唯一来得及阻止他们的人
and I am the only one fast enough to stop them.
我是闪电侠
I am The Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
他是地卜师
His name is Geomancer.
我想见的是红衣人
I'm waiting on the man in red.
终极速度-7快耗尽了
The Velocity-7's wearing off.
-你受伤了吗  -只有我的尊严
- You hurt? - Only my pride.
杰西是我的女儿  极速抓走了她
Jesse's my daughter. Zoom has her.
爸爸  快救我
Daddy, please help me.
不要让他把我关回去  爸爸
Don't let him take me, Daddy.
我说过我们是一个团队
I told you we're a team.
现在你也是其中一员
Now you're a part of it.
我们要帮你救出杰西
We're gonna help you save Jesse.
我们不会让你一个人回去
We're not sending you through alone.
我们一起去地球二号
We're going to Earth-2.
记住杰伊说的  好吗
Just remember what Jay said, okay?
这里的事都有点奇怪
Things here are all sorts of trippy.
凯特琳
Caitlin--
如果你真的了解我
If you knew me at all,
你应该知道我讨厌凯特琳这个名字
you would know that I hate the name Caitlin.
我是冰霜杀手
I'm Killer Frost.
小心
Look out!
爸爸
Dad!
你杀了我父亲  你个贱婊子
You killed my father, you evil bitch.
你不该与穿越者为伍
You shouldn't have palled around with a breacher.
-闪电侠  救我们  -不
- Flash, save us! - No!
极速要活捉他
Zoom wanted him alive.
你知道不听极速的指示有什么下场
You know what Zoom will do if you don't obey him.
不
No!
看看周围  闪电侠
Look around, Flash.
这是你最后
This is the last place
看见的地方
you'll ever see.
地球二
我知道你在这里  哈里森·威尔斯
I know you're here, Harrison Wells,
而且你不是一个人回来的
and you did not come alone.
你可以尽力藏起来
You can try to hide...
但我是现今世上速度最快的人
but I'm the fastest man alive.
把威尔斯抓给我
我会把这个城市翻个底朝天
I will scour this city
直到我找到你
until I hunt you down.
一旦我找到了你
And when I do,
把威尔斯
抓给我
你们所有人就尝尝我的狂怒吧
all of you will feel my wrath.
据中城时报的消息  在莫名消失了数月后
CCPN is reporting that Dr. Harrison Wells, the infamous founder of S.T.A.R. Labs
声名狼藉的尖端实验室创始人哈里森·威尔斯
who uncharacteristically has gone unseen
如今受到了通缉
for nearly four months is now a wanted man.
把威尔斯
抓给我
极速追捕哈里森·威尔斯
不久前  极速在整个中城
These images and messages went up moments ago
散步了这些图片和消息
throughout Central City by Zoom.
你看52频道了吗
Have you seen channel 52?
威尔斯博士你在这里不安全  极速在追捕你
You're not safe here, Dr. Wells. Zoom's looking for you.
我知道他在干什么  警戒起来
I know what he's doing. Alert security.
疏散尖端实验室  封锁设施
Evacuate S.T.A.R. Labs. Lock down the facility.
-那你怎么办  -别担心我  亨利
- What about you? - Don't worry about me, Henry.
现在先把所有人都弄出去
Just get everyone out of here now.
快  行动
Now! Go!
哈里
Harry!
别开枪
Don't shoot!
妈的  拉蒙
Damn it, Ramon.
艾伦在哪
Where's Allen?
-极速抓走了他  -什么
- Zoom took him. - What?
我们追踪了死亡风暴和冰霜杀手
We tracked down Deathstorm and Killer Frost,
还见到了我的二重身  回波
met my doppelganger, Reverb--
超级大恶人  超级恶能力
super evil guy, super evil powers.
他们三个差点干掉巴里
The three of them almost took down Barry until
后来极速出现了  因为追捕极速者
Zoom showed up, killed Cisco-2,
杀了西斯科2号和死亡风暴
killed Deathstorm for hurting a speedster.
但给冰霜杀手留了活口
But then he left Killer Frost alive
然后带走了巴里
and then took off with Barry.
那你怎么还活着
How are you still alive?
估计他比你还不在乎我  哈里
Looks like he cares even less about me than you do, Harry.
不  不
No, no.
极速做任何事都有原因
Zoom doesn't do anything by accident.
他跟踪你了吗
Did he follow you here?
《盗火线》我看了无数遍了
I've seen “heat” like 50 times, okay?
我知道怎么甩开跟踪  他没有跟踪我
I know how to shake a tail. He didn't follow me.
你看看这个
But check this out.
我从那个死了的我的二重身那里偷来的
I jacked these from my dead ringer.
我觉得我们可以摆弄一下  用这个找到极速
I think we can tweak these puppies-- use them to find Zoom.
我去  拉蒙  我们没时间这么做
Damn it, Ramon, we don't have time for this.
极速在追捕我们
Zoom is hunting us--
Zoom is hunting us!
我们得另做计划
We need to make an alternate plan,
否则  极速...
because if we don't, Zoom--
别再这样想了  好吗
Stop thinking like that, okay?
我们会找到杰西  找到巴里的
We're gonna find Jesse, and we're gonna find Barry.
我知道我们可以
I know we will.
喂  有人吗
Hello? Is anyone there?
无论这是谁干的
Okay, whoever's responsible for this,
出来我们吵一架
boy, we're gonna have words,
就我们俩
the two of us, okay?
这  这太过分了
This is-- this is not okay.
巴里2号
Barry-2.
威尔斯博士  真是让人失望
Dr. Wells,this is very disappointing.
你们俩应该以你们的行为为耻
I mean, the two of you should be ashamed of yourselves.
你们不能就这样把一个人锁在屋里
You can't just lock someone in a room like this.
我在这里呆多久了
How long was I in here for?
差不多一天
Barely a day.
一天
One day?
天呢  我妻子要担心死了
Oh, jeez, my wife's gonna be worried sick.
-威尔斯博士  -怎么了
- Dr. Wells. - Yeah?
博士  我不清楚你知道与否
Doctor, I'm not sure if you're aware of this,
我的夫人是中城警局里一位
but my wife is a very well-respected detective
令人尊敬的警探
in the Central City Police Department.
她对此一定会非常不满
She's got to be very upset.
真是麻烦
Whoa, this is heavy.
当然是了
It certainly is.
不好意思  各位
And I'm sorry, fellas,
但我要求你们立即告诉我
but I demand to know what the heck
到底发生了什么
is going on here this instant.
巴里  这说来话长
Barry, this is a very long story.
长到我们现在没时间告诉你
One that we don't have time to tell right now.
我们很抱歉把你关起来了一天
We're sorry we locked you in that room
但现在  你必须离开
for a day, but right now, you need to leave.
你必须集合...
You need to gather--
警告
他来了
He's here.
不许动
Do not move.
威尔斯和他的朋友在哪
Where are Wells and his friends?
威尔斯博士  到底发生了什么
Dr. Wells, hey, what the heck is going on?
极速在追捕我们
Oh, Zoom's after us.
极速  为什么极速要追你们
Zoom? What do-- Why would Zoom be after you?
这就是我刚才要跟你讲的故事的一部分
That's part of that long story I was telling you about.
我不知道我是否能
I don't know if I can
面对这种事情
deal with something like this.
-你有时间穹顶  -是的
- You have a time vault? - Yeah.
我是极速的敌人  我需要躲藏的地方
I'm an enemy of Zoom, and I need a place to hide
以防类似这种情况出现
when something like this happens.
-进去  -遵命
- Get in! - Yes, sir.
那是极速  那是极速
That's Zoom! That's Zoom!
拉蒙
Ramon...
让他闭嘴
Shut him up.
好吧
Okay.
呼吸  呼吸  呼吸
Breathe, breathe, breath, breath...
假墙
Fake wall.
他不会再被假墙骗到了
He's not gonna fall for another fake wall.
我们得转移
We need to move.
我们得找其他地方躲藏
We need to find a different place to hide
然后制定个计划
and make a plan.
等等  等等
Wait, wait...
不行
No.
我觉得在咱们干其他事之前
I think before we do anything,
你得向我解释当下
you have to explain to me everything
发生的一切
that is going on here.
你在浪费时间
You're wasting your time.
我刚来的时候也以为能逃出去
I used to think I could escape too when I first got here.
没有出路的
There's no way out.
那是谁
Who is that?
我不知道
I don't know.
极速把我抓来这里的时候他就在了
He's been here since Zoom brought me to this place.
住手  好吗
Stop, okay?
别再敲了
Just--just please stop.
杰西  我想他在试图帮助我们
Jesse, I think he might be trying to help us.
我们没救了
Nothing is gonna help us.
不是这样的
That's not true.
我们会逃出这里
We're gonna get out of here.
你爸爸会找到我们的  我保证
Your dad's gonna find us, I promise.
你还真信任一个只关心自己的人
You sure have a lot of faith in a man who only cares about himself.
你知道吗  我一开始
You know, I actually thought that
也那样认为
at first too.
但那不是真的
It's not true.
我们见面后  他所作出的每一个决定
Every decision that he's made--
他所做出的每一个行动
every action he's taken since we've met--
都是为了救你
has been to save you.
你爸爸没有放弃你  杰西
Your dad hasn't given up on you, Jesse.
不要放弃他
Don't give up on him.
随便你怎么想
Believe what you want,
但是你活着的唯一原因
but the only reason that you're still alive
是好让我在你父亲面前杀了你
is so I can kill you in front of your father.
而你父亲活着的唯一原因
And the only reason your father's still alive...
是为了帮我获得你的速度
Is to get me your speed.
一旦完成了目的
Once he does that,
他也会死
he will die too.
地球一
一段沉寂之后
Up after the break,
能引发地震的超能力者让民众恐惧并好奇
earthquake-causing meta-human leaves citizens shaken and wondering,
闪电侠去哪了
where is The Flash?
完成了
It's finished.
缺口又稳定了
Breach stabilized again.
巴里  西斯科和威尔斯有20小时的时间回来
Barry, Cisco, and Wells have 20 hours to get back.
你太棒了
You're amazing.
如果说是稳定缺口的话  或许如此...
When it comes to stabilizing breaches, maybe--
但是对于与超能力者战斗来说就不行了
not so much when it comes to fighting meta-humans.
你是有点手生了
You were a little rusty.
我是太慢了
I was too slow.
地卜师还在外肆虐  凯瑟琳
Geomancer's still out there, Caitlin.
恐慌民众好奇闪电侠在哪
必须要阻止他
He has to be stopped.
我需要准备好迎接他下一次攻击
I have to be ready in case he attacks again.
还有多长时间  那终极速度...
How much longer till the Velocity...
八
8.
终极速度-8才能准备好
Velocity-8 is ready?
我需要稳定化合物
I need to finalize the compound--
确保细胞外基质保持完成
make sure the extracellular matrix stays intact
这样你就不会那么快失去速度
so you don't lose your speed as fast.
好的  太好了
Okay, great.
怎么了
What is it?
上一次对战地卜师之后
After your last encounter with Geomancer,
我做了些测试
I ran some tests.
终极速度-7对你体内
The Velocity-7 is reacting
受损的细胞产生了反应
with the damaged cells in your body.
导致了更严重的细胞退化
It's causing more cellular degeneration.
我相信下一批药不会产生同样的影响
Well, I have faith that the next batch won't do the same thing.
杰伊  我不能继续给你会伤害你的东西
Jay, I can't keep giving this to you if it's hurting you.
如果它能帮我打败地卜师
If it'll help me defeat Geomancer,
你可能必须要给
you might have to.
直到巴里回来
Till Barry gets back,
我可能是这座城唯一的救星
I may be the only chance this city has.
中城新闻图报
我简直不敢相信
I don't know how this is possible,
但是你居然让篮球
but you somehow made basketball
听起来比棒球还无聊
sound more boring than baseball.
改了
Fix this.
斯科特·埃文斯  你的新编辑
Scott Evans, your new editor.
-爱瑞丝  -韦斯特  我知道
- Oh, Iris-- - West, I know.
你写了近期地卜师攻击的报道
You wrote the story about the recent Geomancer attack.
-是的  我写了  -我不能发表
- Yeah, I did. - I'm not running that.
什么  为什么
What, why?
那是篇想安抚民心的烂文
It's a fluff piece to try to make people feel good.
他们需要知道的是真相
What they need to know is the truth;
闪电侠也许不能总是救他们
The Flash might not always be there to save them.
你不同意吗
You disagree?
他救了城市里很多的人
I think that he's saved a lot of people in this city.
那他现在在哪
But where is he now?
我需要一个真正的故事
I need to run a real story.
好吧
Okay, uh--
如果我能给你写篇
what if I could get you an exclusive
与地卜师战斗过的超能力者专访呢
with the meta-human that fought Geomancer?
是  另一个闪电侠
This--this other Flash.
怎么  你也和他是朋友吗
What, you friends with him too?
只需要  给我一点时间
Just, um, give me a little time.
好吧  但是如果还是你之前写的那种垃圾
Fine, but if it's the same as the other crap that you wrote,
我就要刊登一篇关于闪电侠
I'm gonna run something about how The Flash
也许不是他们梦中英雄的文章
may not be the hero we all dreamed he was.
艾瑞丝  艾瑞丝
Iris- - hey, Iris.
巴里  你昨晚去哪了
Barry, where were you last night?
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我父亲昨晚死了
My father died yesterday,
你却一直没回家
and you never even came home.
我知道  我知道  我听说了
I know, I know. I heard.
我真的  真的很抱歉
I'm so, so sorry.
你听说了  你在场的  巴里
You--you heard? You were there, Barry.
其实我不在
I actually was not there.
我要  好吧  好吧
I'm--I'm gonna-- yeah, okay. Okay, look.
来我的实验室  来我的实验室就是了
Come to my lab. Just come up to my lab.
我会向你解释一切  好吗
I'm gonna explain everything, okay?
我会解释的
I'm gonna explain it.
所以昨天的巴里不是你
So the Barry from yesterday was not you?
不是
No.
你看  我知道
No, look, I--I know
这有点难以相信
that this is hard to believe,
我是说  这真的很像那部科幻剧
but I mean, it is just like that sci-fi series,
《指挥官卡尔：宇宙的太空警长》
Commander Carl, Space Marshal of the Galaxy,
卡尔被吸进了黑洞
where Carl gets sucked into a black hole
结果掉落在了他以为是地球的其他星球上
and ends up on another planet that he thinks is Earth,
但其实是
but really it's Earth...
另一个宇宙的地球
of another universe.
你们  难道你们没有...
Have--have you guys not s--
那一集太有创意了  你们应该去看看
Oh, it's a seminal episode. You should check it out.
所以昨天你才没有戴结婚戒指
So that's why you weren't wearing your wedding ring yesterday.
而那一吻很...
and-and that-that kiss was-was so--
对不起  他对你动手动脚了吗
I'm-I'm sorry. He got frisky with you?
不不不
No, no, no, no, no.
好  我要找出这个人
Okay, I'm gonna have to find this guy
把我的想法告诉他
and give him a piece of my mind.
别说太多
Don't give him too much.
你丈夫跟我们说你一直在追查极速
Your husband tells us you've been tracking Zoom.
是的  我一直在找他  为什么
Yeah, I've been trying to. Why?
-我们要找出他的巢穴  -巢穴
- We need to find his lair. - Lair?
他是坏蛋  我把那叫做巢穴
He's a bad guy; I'm calling it a lair.
极速在找你
Zoom is looking for you.
你们为什么要找他
Why are you going after him?
极速抓了我女儿
Zoom has my daughter
和我们的巴里  我们要把他们俩救出来
and our Barry, and we need to rescue them both.
和所有的人一样
Look, I want to find Zoom
我也想要找到极速  但是没人能追踪到他
just as much as anybody, but no one can track him.
只有跟他合作的超能力者
The only person who would know where he would be hiding someone
才知道他藏匿人质的地方
would be a meta that's worked with him.
冰霜杀手那样的超能力者
A meta like Killer Frost?
也许吧
Yeah, maybe.
但是极速饶了她一命
But Zoom kept her alive yesterday
因为她总是服从他
because she always obeys him.
她是不可能告诉我们他的下落的
There is no way that she's gonna tell you where he is.
这就不一定了
I'm not so sure about that.
如果她对死亡风暴的爱像凯特琳对罗尼那样
If she loved Deathstorm as much as my Caitlin loved Ronnie,
我认为极速杀死他  她一定会伤心欲绝
I think she'd be more than upset at Zoom for killing him.
找到她就跟找到极速一样困难
Look, finding her is gonna be just as hard as finding Zoom.
但如果有什么人能找到她
But if anyone can do it...
非我丈夫莫属了
my husband can.
没错
Right, yes.
我是可以
I can, actually.
好吧
Um, all right.
貌似帕蒂·斯皮沃特曾是犯罪现场调查技术人员
Okay, well it looks like Patty Spivot was a CSI tech
调查过多起冰霜杀手的案件
on most of the Killer Frost cases.
查得还相当地彻底
She's pretty thorough, so...
那是什么
What's that?
这是冰霜杀手的超能力数据
Oh, this is Killer Frost meta-data
是从众多犯罪现场收集来的
collected from numerous crime scenes--
有DNA追踪动向  面部识别
DNA trace movements, facial recognition,
特别针对她的温度波动
temperature fluctuations specific to her.
我的算法把所有的数据进行编译
My algorithm compiles all the data
然后给出我们一个大体位置
and gives us an approximate location.
对大多数超能力者都有效  当然除了极速
It works on most metas, except for Zoom, of course.
他移动太快  从未留下踪迹
He's too fast-- never leaves a trace.
有了
Okay.
看来最佳的位置是在林地
Looks like the best bet's the Woodlands.
中城最好的犯罪现场调查
Best CSI in Central City.
你知道在哪里吧
You know where that is, right?
-知道  -走吧
- Yeah. - Let's go.
等等  我跟你们一起去
Wait, I'm going with you guys.
-你们会需要人帮忙的  -好
- You're gonna need some help. - Okay.
爱瑞丝  我
Iris, I--
巴里  我父亲
Barry, Zoom and his followers
是被极速和他的同伙害死的
are the reason that my father is dead.
如果我能阻止他继续杀人
If I can stop him from killing anyone else,
我会尽力一试
I'm gonna try.
好  那我也一起去
Okay, then I'm coming too.
-不  -不
- No. - No.
巴里  这不是你该做的事
Barry, this is not what you do.
我知道
I know that.
但我也知道约瑟夫不太喜欢我
But I also know Joseph didn't like me too much,
可他是我岳父
but he was my father-in-law.
如果你去
If you're going,
我要跟你一起去
I am coming with you.
好吧
All right.
你可以跟着来  但是别妨碍我们
You can come, but you stay out of our way.
这不是摩斯密码
That's not Morse code.
我知道他有话想和我们说
I know he's trying to tell us something.
我们只是要找出规律
We just have to find the pattern.
没有规律可循  巴里
There's no pattern, Barry.
我很肯定你爸爸
You know, your dad, who I'm pretty sure
无论在哪个世界上都是最聪明的人
is one of the smartest people to live on either of our Earths,
他告诉我唯一比他聪明的人
told me the only person smarter than him
就是你
was you.
他这么说过吗
He said that?
如果是真的
If that's true,
我们一起联手
we work together--
我知道我们能搞清楚
I know we can figure this out.
值得一试吧
Worth a shot?
好
Okay.
他的连续敲击不会超过五次
Well, he never goes past five.
什么
What?
他连续敲击五次就会暂停
He never goes past five knocks without pausing.
对不对  仔细听
Right? Listen.
你说得对
Hey, you're right.
我好像
I think--
知道是什么意思
I think I know what that is.
这是战俘使用的五乘五敲击密码
It's a five-by-five tap code used by POWs.
只会给出我们二十五个字母
That would only get us to 25 letters,
而字母表有二十六个字母
and there's 26 in the alphabet.
但如果你把C和K集合在一起就不同了
Not if you combine C and K.
这两个字母听起来都一样
They sound the same.
试试看吧
Let's try it out.
-值得一试  -好
- Worth a shot. - All right.
好了
There it is.
好像跟之前的有所不同
Looks different than before.
那是因为我发现终极速度-8
That's because I realized that there was a flaw
有缺陷
with Velocity-8,
所以我重新配方了细胞外基质  就有了
so I reformulated the extracellular matrix, and...
终极速度-9
Velocity-9.
人们都说
You know what they say:
第九次尝试时才取得成功
ninth time's the charm.
爱瑞丝  你没事吧
Hey, Iris. You okay?
没事  只是有点担心时间
Yeah, I'm just a little worried about the time.
别担心
Well, don't worry.
在我们关闭缺口前  他们会回来的
They'll make it back before we close the breach.
其实我来是有别的事要和你说
Um, actually I was here to talk to you about something else.
说吧  什么事
Oh. Yeah, sure. What is it?
我的新编辑
Well, my new editor
想要我写一篇尖锐的文章
wants me to write a scathing article
关于闪电侠无法保护中城
on The Flash not being able
受到地卜师的攻击
to protect Central City from Geomancer.
不是吧
Really?
是的
Yeah.
我倒是希望能写一篇关于你的文章
I was hoping to write an article about you instead--
以此来平复民众的情绪  直到巴里回来
something that would calm people until Barry got back.
你知道的  爱瑞丝
You know, Iris,
我不知道这个想法好不好
I don't know if that's the best idea.
我认为如果大家
Well, I think that if people
知道有人能保护他们
knew that there was someone that could protect them,
会
it would--
会起到帮助的作用
it would really help.
你能考虑一下吗
Would you just think about it?
疯狂的警报响了
Some crazy alarm's going off.
是的
Yeah.
别妄想逃跑
Don't even think about running.
突发新闻
市里出现了新闪电侠
There's a new Flash in town.
就是戴着闪亮头盔的那个
You know, the one with the shiny helmet.
虽然不是我想要击垮的那个极速者
Not the speedster I was hoping to crack,
但是我们来看看他有多快吧  中城
but let's see just how fast he is, Central City.
给我终极速度-9
Give me the Velocity-9.
杰伊  我们不知道能持续多久
Jay, we have no idea how long it will last.
没时间管那么多了  凯特琳
We don't have time to figure that out, Caitlin.
杰伊
Jay?
我没事
I'm okay.
就是消耗了我很多体力
That just took a lot out of me.
但是感觉确实很好
But it sure felt good.
刚才真是太棒了  杰伊
That was amazing, Jay.
谢谢  我自己也很惊讶  说真的
Thanks. I kind of surprised myself, to be honest.
凯特琳才是功臣
Caitlin deserves all the credit.
看来你的终极速度-9很成功
Looks like your Velocity-9's a winner.
我还需要做进一步的测试
I still need to run some tests.
爱瑞丝  关于那个采访
Iris, about the interview, um--
我想我已经有了所需的一切素材
I think that I have everything that I need.
太好了
Great.
因为我真的需要睡上一觉
'Cause I could really use a nap.
我就在楼下
I'll, uh, be downstairs.
第二行  第五个
Two down, five across.
-是字母J  -J吗
- It's J. - J?
这就是你想敲的吗  字母J
That's what you're tapping-- the letter J?
好的  下一个呢
All right, what's next?
字母A
A.
好的
All right.
第五行
Five down...
第四个  字母Y
Four across. Y.
J-A-Y
J-a-y?
你拼的是杰伊
You're spelling Jay.?
是指杰伊·加里克吗
As in Jay Garrick?
他  他活着
He's--he's alive.
但他在我的地球上
But he's on my Earth.
停下 停下
Stop, stop-- hey--
停  听着  我很抱歉
stop-- look, I'm sorry.
我不知道你什么意思
I don't know what you mean.
杰伊·加里克没有和我们一起来
Jay Garrick didn't come with us.
听着  请接着敲吧
Look, just keep tapping, please.
我们不明白
We don't understand.
求你了
Please.
别再和他们说话了
Don't talk to them again.
我会逃出这里的
I'm gonna get out of here.
然后我会毁灭你
And I'm gonna destroy you.
我想得到的只是你的速度  闪电侠
All I need from you is your speed, Flash.
而只要你还勉强活着
And you only need to be barely alive
我就可以取到
for me to get it.
别打了
Stop!
巴里
Barry...
巴里  你还好吗
Barry, are you okay?
我没事
I'm okay.
极速刚刚教了我怎么逃出这里
Zoom just showed me how to get out of this thing.
你确定是这个地方吗
You're sure this is the place?
肯定是这个地方
This is definitely the place.
你们迷路了吗
You lost?
还是又回来找乐子了
Or just back for more fun?
我们只想过来谈谈
We just came here to talk.
真的吗
Oh, really?
你们每次聊天的时候
Do you bring your little toys
都带着这些小玩具吗
to every conversation you have?
还是说你们想看我再次受煎熬
Or do you just want to see me burn again?
考虑到你杀了我父亲
Considering you killed my father,
我确实有过这个想法
the thought has crossed my mind.
告诉我们
Tell us--
极速把他的俘虏都关在哪里
where does Zoom keep his prisoners?
你真的不知道该怎么用你的能力
You really don't know how to use your abilities,
对吧  穿越者
do you, breacher?
我在努力掌握呢  艾尔莎
It's a work in progress, Elsa.
极速杀了你的一生挚爱
Zoom killed the love of your life.
你一定很受伤
This hurts,
哪怕是像你这样冷血的人
even for somebody with a heart as cold as yours.
所以你觉得这会让我和极速反目成仇吗
And you think that would make me turn on Zoom?
敌人的敌人就是我的朋友  不是吗
Enemy of my enemy is my friend, right?
什么  可别告诉我这套在这里不管用
What--don't tell me it doesn't work like that over here.
如果我告诉你
If I tell you,
他就会杀了我
he'll kill me.
但如果我杀了你
But if I kill you
再把你带给他
and take you to him,
我敢打赌他会对我感到很满意
I bet he'd be pretty pleased with me.
说不定甚至会放我一马
Maybe even let me off my leash.
所以你大胆猜测一下
So take a wild guess.
我会作何选择呢
What do you think I'm gonna choose?
快跑
Move!
这可和计划的不一样
That did not go as planned!
她的名字里有杀手两字
Her name starts with Killer.
你难道还会对这反应感到惊讶吗
This comes as a shock to you?
我们现在必须得逃
We got to move now!
-我来掩护你  -好的
- I will cover you. - Okay.
不不不  这是一个坏主意
No, no, no, hey, that's a horrible idea.
别啊  别这样
Hey, no! Hey, hey, no!
你们
Hey, guys--
停下
Stop--
不然就让你再也不能发冰柱玩儿
or you'll never make another icicle again.
DNA样本: 杰伊·加里克
真是不敢相信
I can't believe it.
怎么了
What is it?
我觉得我想出该怎么救杰伊的命了
I think I figured out how to save Jay's life.
杰伊  醒醒啊
Hey, Jay-- uh, wake up.
快到表层控制室来  有重要的事
Come to the cortex. It's important.
可不是嘛
It certainly is.
你想干什么
What do you want?
我想看一个英雄倒下
I like to watch heroes fall
而再无翻身之地
and never get back up.
他总会东山再起的
He always gets back up.
当地球把你吞噬的时候  就很难做到了吧
Hard to do that when the Earth swallows you whole.
它在哪儿
Where is it?
别走啊
Aw, don't go.
我们玩得正开心呢
We're having so much fun.
我的天啊  凯特琳
Oh, my God! Caitlin!
凯特琳  你还好吗
Caitlin, are you okay?
看来这个新闪电侠也不算是什么英雄啊
Looks like this new Flash isn't much of a hero after all.
我们看看七级地震对尖端科研实验室有何影响
Let's see what a seven will do to S.T.A.R. Labs.
好枪法
Nice shot.
我本来想射他的腿的
I was aiming for his leg.
极速的老巢在哪里
Where is Zoom's lair?
在哪儿
Where is it?
如果我告诉你
If I tell you,
他会杀了我的
he will kill me.
他本来就是要杀你  凯特琳
He'll kill you anyway, Caitlin.
别这么叫我  这不是我的名字
Stop calling me that. It's not my name.
不  这就是
Yes, it is.
你只是不想听到它
You just don't want to hear it
因为它让你想起你过去的样子
because it reminds you of someone you used to be.
相信我  我很了解曾经的你
Trust me, I know that person very well.
你对我一无所知
You don't know anything about me.
我了解在我那个地球上的凯特琳·斯诺
I know the Caitlin Snow on my Earth.
我知道当她爱某个人的时候
I know that when she loves someone,
那个人就是她的整个世界
that person is her world.
那个人是罗尼·雷蒙德
That person was Ronnie Raymond.
而他也死了
And he died too.
这击垮了她
It devastated her,
而我能看出来对你也是一样
and I can see it's doing the same to you.
这是极速干的
Zoom took that.
他的女儿  我的朋友
His daughter-- my friend--
他会从我们身边夺走他们
he's gonna take them away from us,
就像他把罗尼从你身边夺去一样
just like he took Ronnie from you.
凯特琳
Caitlin...
你只要告诉我们他把他们藏哪儿了
All you have to do is tell us where he's keeping them.
我们就再也不会来打扰你
And then you'll never hear from us again,
你就可以远走高飞了
and you can go.
拜托了
Please.
好吧
Fine.
我会带你们去
I'll show you where it is.
但仅此而已
But that's it.
那我们要去哪儿
Uh, where are we going?
登天崖壁
Ascension Cliffs.
你确定要一直试下去吗
Look, are you sure you want to keep doing that?
你知道如果极速抓住你
You know, if Zoom catches you,
他会再揍你一顿的
he's gonna hurt you again.
我不明白为什么穿不过去
I don't understand why I can't phase through this.
你的身体的震动频率需要和
Well, your body would need to have the same resonance
那面玻璃墙相同
as the glass walls.
我已经够快的了
I should be going more than fast enough.
是别的原因
It's something else.
也许你发生共鸣的频率不一致
Maybe you're resonating at a different frequency.
没错  你们地球的震动频率和我们不一样
Yeah, your Earth vibrates at a different frequency than mine.
所以西斯科才用不了震波
Same reason Cisco can't vibe.
有办法弥补这种差距吗
Is there any way to make up the difference?
只要我能更快些
Only if I can go faster.
我们要去那上面吗
We're going up there?
极速的老巢就在那
That's where Zoom's lair is.
只有极速者能达到的地方
A place only a speedster could get to.
这简直是"疯狂悬崖"
There are like the Cliffs of Insanity.
那我们要怎么上去
So how do we get up there?
我能给你制造些抓手  亲爱的
I can make you something to climb on, darling.
你是认真的吗  你想让我们...
Are you serious? You want us to--
就这么攀爬到悬崖顶端吗
what, just climb to the top of those cliffs--
就踩着冰
on ice?
你有更好的主意吗
Got any better ideas?
没有  女士  我只是...
No, ma'am, I'm just, you know, I--
我...我穿着皮鞋呢
I've got--you know, I'm wearing wingtips here.
这种鞋不怎么防滑
They, um, don't have much tread.
巴里
Barry.
巴里  也许你该等在后边
Barry, um, maybe you should stay behind.
好吗
Yeah?
不  不行
No--hey, no.
我不会让你一个人上去的
I'm not letting you go up there by yourself.
你不愿意去没关系的
It is okay if you don't want to go--
不想去就不去
if you don't want to do this.
你是我妻子
You are my wife.
我不会离开你身边
I'm not leaving your side.
好吧
Okay.
可以走了吗
Can we go?
-好的  -我准备好了
- Yeah. - I'm ready.
趁我改变主意之前快走吧
Let's go before I change my mind.
你真以为手铐能阻止我
You really think handcuffs can stop me?
我知道可以
I know they can--
就像你脖子上的这个项圈
just like this boot on your neck.
可以抑制你的能力
It dampens your power.
还有你将会称之为家的
Same goes for the six-by-six cell
铁山监狱里六乘六大小的牢房
you'll be calling home at Iron Heights.
好了  走吧
All right, let's go.
凯特琳
Caitlin.
抱歉我来晚了
So sorry I didn't come sooner.
没关系
That's okay, um...
能给你看点东西吗
can I show you something?
我的细胞
My cells...
它们不再衰退了
they've stopped degenerating?
这怎么可能呢
How is this even possible?
看起来终极速度-9在你体内时
It appears that when the Velocity-9 is in your system,
可以激活你潜在的细胞再生能力
it kick-starts your latent regenerative capabilities,
你的细胞开始自我修复了
and your cells repair themselves.
你有办法让它永久有效吗
And do you think you can get this to work permanently?
不知道  但我们的方向是正确的
I don't know, but I think we're on the right track.
凯特琳  我不知道说什么好
Caitlin, I don't know what to say.
这真是...你真是...
This is--you are--
什么情况
What was that?
是神速炮
The speed cannon.
一定是地卜师的震动损坏了它
Geomancer's tremors must have damaged it.
故障-M2
好了  来吧
Okay, come on.
过来
Come on!
缺口不稳定了
The breach isn't stabilized.
我们必须尽快修好
We need to fix this fast.
否则他们再也无法回来了
Otherwise they're never gonna be able to come back.
原来我们听到的是这个声音
So that was the sound that we heard.
请告诉我实际上没有这么糟
Please tell me it's not as bad as it looks.
不会吧  当真吗
Come on, seriously?
返程时间还有一小时
They still have an hour left.
他们现在会不会正在穿越缺口
What if they're trying to get through the breach right now
却过不来
and they can't?
震动破坏了夸克物质
Okay, the jolt disrupted the quark matter.
电磁绝缘子正在失效
The electromagnetic insulators are failing.
如何才能及时修好
How do we fix this in time?
能不能修好都难说
I don't know if we can.
巴里
Barry?
西斯科
Cisco?
伙计  我们成功了
Dude, we made it.
你们是怎么找到这里的
How did you find this place?
有人帮忙
Had some help.
我都懒得吐槽这家伙了
Don't even get me started on this guy.
天啊
Oh, boy.
威尔斯博士
Dr. Wells...
退后
Stand back.
我来了
I'm here.
来吧  我们一起出去吧
Come on, let's get you out of here.
好了
Okay.
冰霜
Frost?
帮帮忙
A little help?
我们没有这个约定
Not part of the deal.
冰霜
Frost!
带我们来也不是约定好的
Bringing us up here wasn't part of the deal, either,
但你来了
but here you are.
直觉告诉我  你没有我想像中
Something tells me you're not as cold
那么冷酷无情
as I thought you were.
也许有  也许没有
Maybe, maybe not.
怎么回事  为什么不起作用了
What's going on? Why--why isn't it working?
我不知道
I don't know.
我从没出现这种问题
I've never had this problem before.
威尔斯博士
Dr. Wells...
碳炔
Carbyne.
是某种形态的碳炔
It's some form of carbyne.
这座牢笼是用某种形态的碳炔做的
This cell's made out of some form of carbyne.
冰冻是没办法救他出来的
You'll never be able to freeze him out of there.
你没法穿过来吗
You can't phase out of there?
你们走吧
Just go, all right?
趁极速回来前
Before Zoom comes back.
我们不会把你留在这
We're not leaving you here.
我无法逃脱这座牢笼
I can't get out of this cell.
我试过了
I've tried
很多次
a lot.
我的速度还不足以穿过这面墙
I'm not fast enough to phase through this.
你们得...
You got--
快走吧  好吗
just leave, all right?
快走吧
Just leave.
你知道  我们费了多大劲
Do you know what we did
才到这里吗  巴里
to get here, Barry?
我们说服了她
We convinced her--
冰霜杀手
Killer Frost--
来给我们引路
to show us the way.
然后我们爬上了外面陡峭的悬崖
Then we climbed some insanely steep cliffs
是踩着冰做的支点爬的
outside on footholds made of ice--
是冰啊
ice.
我们都冒着生命危险
And all of us risked our lives,
明知道极速在追捕我们还是要去救杰西
knowing Zoom was after us, to rescue Jesse...
救你
and you.
我不认识你
Now, I don't know you,
你也不认识我
and you don't know me,
但我要告诉你
but I can tell you that today,
今天我  我做到了我从不认为可能的事情
I--I did things that I never thought possible,
因为我要向我妻子证明
because I needed to prove to my wife
向我自己证明我可以
and to myself that I could.
既然我今天能够实现不可能
Now, if I can do the impossible today,
你也可以
so can you.
我只是巴里·艾伦
I'm just Barry Allen,
但你是闪电侠
but you're The Flash.
如果你告诉自己
If you tell yourself
你可以逃出这里
you can phase out of there,
你就能做到
you'll do it.
好吧  我们走
Okay, let's go.
-快走  -等一下
- Go, come on. - Wait, wait!
我们不能抛下他
We're not leaving him.
巴里  没时间了
Barry, there's no time.
他哪也去不了
He's not going anywhere,
你们也是
and neither are any of you.
谢谢你
Thank you
带他们到我面前
for bringing them to me.
你出卖我们
You double-crossed us?
他杀了罗尼
He killed Ronnie!
看来我的心正如你想的那样冰冷
Guess my heart is as cold as you thought after all.
我简直无法相信
I can't believe you.
你要知道  另一个你会对你
Just so you know, you would be very disappointed
非常失望
in you right now.
极速
Zoom.
放他们走
Let them go.
你要的只是我和巴里
All you need is me and Barry.
你说的没错
You're right.
我也许还不能杀掉你们
I may not be able to kill you yet,
但我能杀他们
but I can kill them.
不  不
No, no! No...
我跟你说过我会在你父亲面前杀了你
I told you I'd kill you in front of your father.
不  不
No! No!
不
No...
快离开
Get out of here.
凯特琳
Caitlin.
你说得对
You were right.
他杀了罗尼
He killed Ronnie.
谢谢
Thank you.
我不会抛下他离开的
I'm not leaving without him.
巴里  没时间了
Barry, there's no time.
没时间了
There's no time!
我拖不了多久
I can't hold him forever.
我会在一切结束之后回来找你的
Hey, I'm coming back for you when this is over, all right?
快走
Go!
我会回来的
I'm coming back!
杰伊  我们得做点什么
Jay, we need to do something.
我们只能重启电磁绝缘子
Our only chance is to reboot the electromagnetic insulators
希望夸克物质能再平均分布
and hope the Quark Matter redistributes equally.
我们要怎么做
How do we do that?
我们要手动操作
We have to do it manually.
但是在它们启动的时候
But you can't be near the stabilizer rings
你不能靠近稳定环
when they power on,
不然你会被吸进缺口
or you'll get sucked into the breach.
如果我能制出一个漩涡来抵消拉力就不会
Not if I create a vortex to counteract the pull.
你不能同时做到两件事
You can't do both at the same time.
凯特
Cait...
我一定要试试
I have to try.
我帮你
I'll help you.
什么  爸爸  不要
What? Dad, no.
如果这能把巴里带回这个地球  我就要做
Look, if it brings Barry back to this Earth, I'm doing it.
你确定吗
You sure?
我们说得越久  我就会越不确定
The more we talk about it, the less sure I'll be,
所以让我们放手一搏吧
so let's just do it.
好
Okay.
每一个稳定环都有一个超控电门
There's an override switch on every stabilizer ring.
我制出漩涡
I'll create the vortex.
你按下所有电门  应该就能全部重启
And you flip all of them. They should all reboot.
知道了
Got it.
完成之后  你启动神速炮
Once that's done, you power up the cannon.
缺口应该就会稳定下来
The breach should stabilize.
如果它没稳定下来呢
And what if it doesn't?
那我们就不走运了
We're all out of luck.
终极速度9快用完了
The Velocity-9 is running out!
杰伊
Jay!
现在我们知道终极速度9可以维持多久了
I guess now we know how long the Velocity-9 lasts.
-你还好吗  -还好
- Are you okay? - Yeah.
希望他们还好
I just hope they are.
我还好  就是看上去不太好
I'm fine. I'm just a mess.
你们必须离开中城
You need to get out of Central City, all right?
任何你们能够逃离极速魔爪的地方
Any place you think you'll be safe from Zoom.
是的  我们有一些在亚特兰蒂斯的亲人
Yeah, we, um-- we have some family
他们能帮助我们
in Atlantis that can help us.
好的  好
Yeah, okay, good.
你也许没有像我这样
You may not have been struck by lightning
被闪电击中
over here like I was,
但今天  你冒着生命危险
but today, you risked your life
去救你不认识的人
to save somebody you didn't even know.
做英雄就是如此  巴里
That's a hero, Barry.
谢谢你们
Thank you both.
巴里
Barry...
在你的地球上我父亲还活着吗
is my father still alive on your Earth?
是的  他还活着
Yeah, he is.
帮我给他一个拥抱  好吗
Give him a hug for me, will you?
我会的
I will.
你们也要去个安全的地方
You guys need to get someplace safe too.
你们要去哪里
Where are you going?
我们唯一能去的地方
The only place we can.
爸爸  我们不能就这么走了
Dad, we can't just leave.
我们必须走  亲爱的
We have to, honey.
什么  你要我放弃在这里的一切吗
What, you want me to leave everything I have here?
我的朋友  我的家人
My friends, my family--
我的生活
I mean, my life.
你在这不再有生活可言
You don't have a life here anymore.
我也没有
Either do I.
极速太强大了
Zoom is too powerful.
我无法阻止他
I can't stop him.
只要他在这里
And as long as he is here,
他就会捕杀我们至死方休
he's gonna hunt us down until we're dead.
警告
威尔斯  如果你要跟我们走  现在就得离开
Wells, if you're coming with us, we have to go.
时间快到了
It's almost time.
我不管什么时间
I don't care what time it is.
我们做了这么多才稳定住这个缺口
After all we did to stabilize this breach,
在他们出现之前我们都不能关闭它
we're not closing until they show up.
能听到我吗
Y'all hear me?
西斯科
Cisco!
准备永远好关闭缺口吧
Get ready to close the breach for good--
极速要来了
Zoom's coming!
忘带谁了吗  闪电侠
Forgetting someone, Flash?
放开他
Let him go.
关闭缺口
Close the breach.
告诉杰西我爱她
Tell Jesse I love her.
你自己跟她说
Tell her yourself.
不应该那么久的
It shouldn't be taking this long.
关了它  快关了它
Close it! Close it now!
你做到了  你做到了
You did it-- you made it!
巴里
Barry.
不
No!